[{"answer": "I'm good.", "docId": "110407pmt", "aSentId": 10, "question": "Eva, how are you?", "qSentId": 9}, {"answer": "Lovely to have you in my studio.", "docId": "110407pmt", "aSentId": 12, "question": "How are you?", "qSentId": 11}, {"answer": "Occupation.", "docId": "110407pmt", "aSentId": 36, "question": "What do you mean?", "qSentId": 35}, {"answer": "Actor is on there.", "docId": "110407pmt", "aSentId": 38, "question": "What do you call yourself?", "qSentId": 37}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "110407pmt", "aSentId": 52, "question": "That excites me?", "qSentId": 51}, {"answer": "I mean like when you're older you have a better appreciation for history or for knowledge.", "docId": "110407pmt", "aSentId": 59, "question": "Really?", "qSentId": 58}, {"answer": "Chicano studies and political science.", "docId": "110407pmt", "aSentId": 63, "question": "What are you -- what are you actually studying?", "qSentId": 62}, {"answer": "Chicano studies is the study mostly of the Mexican- American movement that has happened in the United States, and the history of Mexican-Americans.", "docId": "110407pmt", "aSentId": 65, "question": "ORGAN: What is Chicano studies?", "qSentId": 64}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "110407pmt", "aSentId": 73, "question": "Can I?", "qSentId": 72}, {"answer": "You can be an honorary Chicano.", "docId": "110407pmt", "aSentId": 75, "question": "You can be an honorary Chicano?", "qSentId": 74}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "110407pmt", "aSentId": 77, "question": "Really?", "qSentId": 76}, {"answer": "Well, you have to help us in the fight for social justice and believe in equality for everyone.", "docId": "110407pmt", "aSentId": 79, "question": "What do I have to do?", "qSentId": 78}, {"answer": "Pretty important.", "docId": "110407pmt", "aSentId": 82, "question": "How important are your roots to you?", "qSentId": 81}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "110407pmt", "aSentId": 94, "question": "You had to learn Spanish?", "qSentId": 93}, {"answer": "I speak a bit of French.", "docId": "110407pmt", "aSentId": 103, "question": "Do you speak French?", "qSentId": 102}, {"answer": "When I came here, I couldn't believe the hot issue it really is.", "docId": "110407pmt", "aSentId": 112, "question": "Immigration?", "qSentId": 111}, {"answer": "Well, that's a loaded question.", "docId": "110407pmt", "aSentId": 126, "question": "How would you fix things?", "qSentId": 125}, {"answer": "I think he had a lot on his plate.", "docId": "110407pmt", "aSentId": 144, "question": "Do you think he has lived up to expectations?", "qSentId": 143}, {"answer": "The great thing about this documentary is that -- actually we produced it so it can be used as a political tool to change the way agricultural workers are treated in the United States.", "docId": "110407pmt", "aSentId": 174, "question": "It's heartbreaking to see kids having to do this in modern ages, isn't it?", "qSentId": 173}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "110407pmt", "aSentId": 189, "question": "ORGAN: You're quite an activist, aren't you?", "qSentId": 188}, {"answer": "I shouldn't be, but I am.", "docId": "110407pmt", "aSentId": 199, "question": "Yes?", "qSentId": 198}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "110407pmt", "aSentId": 240, "question": "How do you deal with that as someone who's got in your own family?", "qSentId": 239}, {"answer": "She's doing amazing.", "docId": "110407pmt", "aSentId": 245, "question": "How is she doing?", "qSentId": 244}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "110407pmt", "aSentId": 278, "question": "To have somebody in your life who none of that means anything to at all and who's not impressed by any of that because why would she be?", "qSentId": 277}, {"answer": "She's very grounding.", "docId": "110407pmt", "aSentId": 280, "question": "It makes it very natural for you, doesn't it?", "qSentId": 279}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "110407pmt", "aSentId": 300, "question": "Don't you find that a bit unsettling when you go home?", "qSentId": 299}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "110407pmt", "aSentId": 303, "question": "No entourage?", "qSentId": 302}, {"answer": "I'm really not a complainer.", "docId": "110407pmt", "aSentId": 318, "question": "What's the matter with you?", "qSentId": 317}, {"answer": "I'm going to go sit in your lap.", "docId": "110407pmt", "aSentId": 323, "question": "Do we say slouch, lay back, think of England?", "qSentId": 322}, {"answer": "Right.", "docId": "110407pmt", "aSentId": 326, "question": "Why do you think I put you in an uncomfortable chair?", "qSentId": 325}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "110407pmt", "aSentId": 332, "question": "Aren't you?", "qSentId": 331}, {"answer": "You know it's funny because Demi Moore and Ashton were, like, you know, the really pioneers of getting everybody on Twitter.", "docId": "110407pmt", "aSentId": 361, "question": "What's the attraction of Twitter?", "qSentId": 360}, {"answer": "No, not drunk tweeting.", "docId": "110407pmt", "aSentId": 386, "question": "Are you a drunk tweeter?", "qSentId": 385}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "110407pmt", "aSentId": 388, "question": "It's more to do with putting stuff out there where you -- why did I do that?", "qSentId": 387}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "110407pmt", "aSentId": 397, "question": "Like if you choose to make your life so private?", "qSentId": 396}, {"answer": "No, because I mean -- really I don't really care.", "docId": "110407pmt", "aSentId": 407, "question": "Because it's so easy now to become a celebrity?", "qSentId": 406}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "110407pmt", "aSentId": 418, "question": "You're look like a mini Oprah, aren't you?", "qSentId": 417}, {"answer": "Well, I think similar to Oprah.", "docId": "110407pmt", "aSentId": 436, "question": "What's the Eva Longoria brand?", "qSentId": 435}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "110407pmt", "aSentId": 443, "question": "Are you tough enough to be a mogul, do you think?", "qSentId": 442}, {"answer": "I am not to be messed with.", "docId": "110407pmt", "aSentId": 452, "question": "Are you not to be messed with?", "qSentId": 451}, {"answer": "Never.", "docId": "110407pmt", "aSentId": 465, "question": "I mean seriously, could you ever go out with a man with a soft handshake?", "qSentId": 464}, {"answer": "I'm not going to name them now.", "docId": "110407pmt", "aSentId": 474, "question": "Who?", "qSentId": 473}, {"answer": "Probably my family.", "docId": "110407pmt", "aSentId": 482, "question": "Who taught you direct eye contact and firm handshake?", "qSentId": 481}, {"answer": "And they're all strong.", "docId": "110407pmt", "aSentId": 486, "question": "They're all strong women, aren't they?", "qSentId": 485}, {"answer": "They're proud.", "docId": "110407pmt", "aSentId": 497, "question": "What do they make -- what do they make of what's happened to you?", "qSentId": 496}, {"answer": "Well, I was always different.", "docId": "110407pmt", "aSentId": 500, "question": "Are they -- do they quite believe it?", "qSentId": 499}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "110407pmt", "aSentId": 507, "question": "Do I like being famous?", "qSentId": 506}, {"answer": "Absolutely.", "docId": "110407pmt", "aSentId": 522, "question": "Or does it make no difference?", "qSentId": 521}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "110407pmt", "aSentId": 531, "question": "Did you imagine you would be married for life?", "qSentId": 530}, {"answer": "Oh, yes.", "docId": "110407pmt", "aSentId": 536, "question": "But did you really believe this was the guy, this was the one for you for life?", "qSentId": 535}, {"answer": "It all came out.", "docId": "110407pmt", "aSentId": 554, "question": "What?", "qSentId": 553}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "110407pmt", "aSentId": 556, "question": "The marriage?", "qSentId": 555}, {"answer": "A bit, yes.", "docId": "110407pmt", "aSentId": 587, "question": "Do you feel humiliated?", "qSentId": 586}, {"answer": "Well, you know, like I said, we just -- you want different things.", "docId": "110407pmt", "aSentId": 593, "question": "What more could a guy want, frankly?", "qSentId": 592}, {"answer": "I don't know.", "docId": "110407pmt", "aSentId": 614, "question": "Is there any way back as far as you're concerned, if a man behaves that way towards you?", "qSentId": 613}, {"answer": "I just got a joint statement, I should tell you, from the Senate Majority Leader Harry Reid and House Speaker John Boehner.", "docId": "110407pmt", "aSentId": 629, "question": "What are you hearing?", "qSentId": 628}, {"answer": "Social and economic issues.", "docId": "110407pmt", "aSentId": 640, "question": "But this is more what about social issues, about these riders that the Republicans are asking for?", "qSentId": 639}, {"answer": "Let's just give you the two biggies.", "docId": "110407pmt", "aSentId": 644, "question": "What issues in particular?", "qSentId": 643}, {"answer": "We started talking about some of the policy issues that aren't so much related to the big fight, which of course is spending and spending cuts.", "docId": "110407pmt", "aSentId": 696, "question": "What are the issues that they're most apart on?", "qSentId": 695}, {"answer": "I love to cook.", "docId": "110407pmt", "aSentId": 736, "question": "Why should I get excited by your cookbook?", "qSentId": 735}, {"answer": "Well, guacamole.", "docId": "110407pmt", "aSentId": 746, "question": "Yes, oh, it's called guac, is it?", "qSentId": 745}, {"answer": "These are my signature things.", "docId": "110407pmt", "aSentId": 752, "question": "Now are these your little signature things?", "qSentId": 751}, {"answer": "I love margaritas.", "docId": "110407pmt", "aSentId": 772, "question": "Now the interview starts, huh?", "qSentId": 771}, {"answer": "It's all very simple and, you know, I'm not a chef.", "docId": "110407pmt", "aSentId": 776, "question": "But this is all quite simple food, isn't it?", "qSentId": 775}, {"answer": "If you can read, you can cook.", "docId": "110407pmt", "aSentId": 786, "question": "Do you think there's someone watching this who can't cook, like me, if they read this book?", "qSentId": 785}, {"answer": "You know, the people you reach.", "docId": "110407pmt", "aSentId": 816, "question": "Why?", "qSentId": 815}, {"answer": "Sex.", "docId": "110407pmt", "aSentId": 823, "question": "Oh, God, what are you going to say?", "qSentId": 822}, {"answer": "She told me that.", "docId": "110407pmt", "aSentId": 837, "question": "Did she tell you that?", "qSentId": 836}, {"answer": "No, it wasn't on air, no.", "docId": "110407pmt", "aSentId": 839, "question": "On air?", "qSentId": 838}, {"answer": "ONGORIA: Good for Gwyn.", "docId": "110407pmt", "aSentId": 846, "question": "None?", "qSentId": 845}, {"answer": "I am.", "docId": "110407pmt", "aSentId": 853, "question": "Is that true?", "qSentId": 852}, {"answer": "No, I don't.", "docId": "110407pmt", "aSentId": 861, "question": "When you see the Oscars on TV, do you think -- do you start practicing the speech that may never happen?", "qSentId": 860}, {"answer": "I actually love --", "docId": "110407pmt", "aSentId": 868, "question": "Do you like politics?", "qSentId": 867}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "110407pmt", "aSentId": 884, "question": "Can you imagine?", "qSentId": 883}, {"answer": "I know.", "docId": "110407pmt", "aSentId": 888, "question": "What about Oprah-Eva ticket?", "qSentId": 887}, {"answer": "You know, people ask me this all the time.", "docId": "110407pmt", "aSentId": 894, "question": "What's been the moment you'd relive tomorrow if you had the chance?", "qSentId": 893}, {"answer": "Well, yes, I just did -- finished a film called \"Cristiada\" with Andy Garcia.", "docId": "110407pmt", "aSentId": 913, "question": "Any movies?", "qSentId": 912}, {"answer": "In the fall.", "docId": "110407pmt", "aSentId": 919, "question": "When's it out?", "qSentId": 918}, {"answer": "OK, we shall.", "docId": "110407pmt", "aSentId": 933, "question": "Let's finish our margaritas, shall we?", "qSentId": 932}]